Who do you think you are?
Do you think you deserve to drink with me?
You're not talking again.
I hate it when you act like this.
What are you so arrogant about?
What do you want to do?
Killing you
was my mission in the first place.
Did you forget?
You two put on a really good show.
Too bad. It was just
a hair's breadth away.
Just like that crate—
you saw something you shouldn't have,
and you put it back exactly as it was.
If we hadn't put special numbers
on the wine bottles,
I'm afraid you two would have fooled us.
We really didn't see anything.
Sorry.
Mr. William only trusts dead men.
Men!
[Eclipse in the Lost City] [Episode 11]
Officer Shen,
you should be able to handle
this many people, right?
Let go of me first.
Do it.
What are you waiting for? Let's go!
After them!
Hurry!
There's a window here.
Are you crazy? It's too high to jump.
They ran to the study!
Hurry!
We have no way out.
They escaped through the back window.
After them to the backyard.
Don't let them leave here alive.
-Yes!
There really is a secret passage.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I'm afraid the foreigners
have occupied this house for so long
without knowing there's such
an unusually devised secret passage.
Are you okay?
Couldn't be better.
Shen Tianbai,
I might die.
Before I die,
can I ask you one last question?
What?
Is it the Shisha Gang
who wants to kill me,
or you?
It's me.
Other people's blood counts too.
Shen Tianbai,
I just saved you.
If I hadn't guessed
that this kind of house
might have a secret passage,
you would have died out there.
Let's go if you're fine.
Shen Tianbai.
Something's wrong.
We've been walking for so long
and haven't found an exit.
And don't you think it's a bit cold here?
I didn't find an exit.
I only found this.
What do we do now?
We can only rest for now
and calm down to think.
Don't you think in such a cold place,
we should sit together?
Why?
So it's easier for you to kill me?
Are you still angry,
Officer Shen?
After all,
we've been through life and death
together.
You have a gun?
Without bullets.
Since we are in the house,
there must be an exit.
Not this way.
Not that way either.
Where is the exit?
Stop.
Don't draw anymore.
You've drawn this path 3 times.
Right.
Where is your chocolate?
Let me look for it.
Here.
Don't flatter yourself.
Save your energy.
Watch over me.
Don't let me die.
There is an exit.
Lu Ye.
The exit is too high.
One of us has to stand
on the other's shoulders to get out.
After getting out,
he can come back to save the other.
You go first.
You...
You saved my life.
I owe you this.
I will come back.
Will you?
I will.
Okay.
I'll help you get out.
You don't trust me?
Of course, I don't trust you.
Would you trust someone
who wants to kill you?
I said I would come back, and I will!
Come back?
With the Shisha Gang to take my life?
No matter what,
I have to get out first.
Lu Ye.
You are the one who won't come back.
Don't come closer!
Lu Ye.
You lied to me again.
Is this your first day knowing me?
Let me go first.
Shoot.
Shen Tianbai, are you crazy?
Is this your first day knowing me?
Do you really think
I wouldn't dare to shoot?
You would.
Of course, you would.
If you kill me,
you won't get out of here alive either.
We'll die together.
You...
You have a fever?
Why are your hands so hot?
Shoot.
I don't kill fools.
I'm not a fool.
Right,
you're not a fool.
That's why you should let me go first.
Why?
Because I remember the way.
You know what?
That map is already in my head.
You won't come back.
I've already sent a message
to Uncle Zhong.
They won't pay attention to you if you go.
You won't come back.
And you're sick.
You won't.
If you go out, we'll both die.
You won't come back.
You won't.
Geez.
I will!
I will come back!
I don't believe you.
You have to believe me.
Geez, it's damaged.
Trust me.
I'll be back before dawn.